[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What element comprises the bulk of Uranus atmosphere?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Ozone", "Carbon Dioxide", "Helium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Beskidy (Beskydy) Euroregion is located in the west part of the Carpathian mountain range. Which three countries does it span?", "correct_answer": "Czech Republic, Poland, Slovakia", "incorrect_answers": ["Hungary, Romania, Ukraine", "Czech Republic, Austria, Slovakia", "Poland, Slovakia, Ukraine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cobras most recognizable feature is its hood, a flap of skin and muscle behind the head, believed to serve this purpose.", "correct_answer": "More threatening appearance", "incorrect_answers": ["Balance control", "Heat collection from sun rays", "Camouflage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does TIA mean in instant messaging language?", "correct_answer": "thanks in advance", "incorrect_answers": ["thats it already", "tony is awesome", "typist is away"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the Giant Panda an endangered species?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This sea animal, widely considered the most valuable shellfish, is common in shallow, warmer waters of all oceans.", "correct_answer": "Oyster", "incorrect_answers": ["Shrimp", "Scallop", "Lobster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are only four questions of value in life. What is sacred? Of what is the spirit made of? What is worth living for? What is worth dying for? The answer to each is the same. Only love. (1995)", "correct_answer": "Don Juan DeMarco", "incorrect_answers": ["When Harry Met Sally", "Cant Hardly Wait", "Ten Things I Hate About You"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Graffiti is plural. This is the singular form.", "correct_answer": "Graffito", "incorrect_answers": ["Graffit", "Graffitius", "Graffitium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jellyfish are vertebrates.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the first balloon flight in the USA take place?", "correct_answer": "1793", "incorrect_answers": ["1839", "1855", "1903"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the sequel to the 2003 movie House of 1000 Corpses?", "correct_answer": "The Devils Rejects", "incorrect_answers": ["Devils Advocate", "House of 2000 Corpses", "Devils in Disguise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unusual ingredient does the traditional Indonesian food called Lawar contain?", "correct_answer": "Raw pig blood", "incorrect_answers": ["Snakes hearts", "Worms", "Bat wings"]}]